[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "whis_er",
      "options": ["T", "P", "F"],
      "answer": "P"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "b_anket",
      "options": ["O", "R", "L"],
      "answer": "L"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "cr_stal",
      "options": ["Y", "I", "O"],
      "answer": "Y"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "dolp_in",
      "options": ["A", "F", "H"],
      "answer": "H"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "thun_er",
      "options": ["D", "P", "Y"],
      "answer": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "_inea__le",
      "options": ["K", "P", "R"],
      "answer": "P"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "m_ster_",
      "options": ["I", "A", "Y"],
      "answer": "Y"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "r_p_tition",
      "options": ["E", "U", "A"],
      "answer": "E"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "o__upation",
      "options": ["S", "C", "L"],
      "answer": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "frie_dship",
      "options": ["L", "O", "N"],
      "answer": "N"
    }
]
